if you still were at the CIA today and you got
the call from the director of CIA and they said,
you know, John, I want you to go find out
because there's so much noise right now in
the marketplace. I want you to go find out
who is actually taking money from Israel,
who's taking money from Qatar, Qatar, who's
taking money from these different organizations,
whether they are trying to get people to give pro-
Zionist messaging or trying to give pro-Islam,
you know, Sharia is not that bad, everything's
okay, or socialism. How quickly would you be able
to find out if someone's getting funded or not? I
I I get that it's a hypothetical question. It's an
FBI issue. The CIA by law would be forbidden
from doing that on Americans, but uh but you
could certainly look at uh at foreign nationals.
The CIA could look at foreign nationals. It you
probably need a couple of months to really dig it
up, but you could dig it up. Would you be able to
find out for a fact? Like if if not all of it. So
the reason why I'm asking is because I had Dominic
Tarjinski here. He is a EU parl member of the
parliament and he tells the story of in 2022 these
multiple EU parliament members were caught getting
ah uh uh what do you call it oh yeah big suffion
one of them was Greek and she she's in prison now
yes yeah $1.5 million of cash you go to that one
Rob where it's one is this one is this the one
yeah So, $1.5 million. But go to if you can go to
uh the picture. Yeah, that's the lady right
there. Whatever her name is, she was part of
the corruption. And apparently there was so much
money in one of the duffel bags that they dropped
$60,000, $60,000 that they caught afterwards
where cash was being given. And then when you
go even deeper, you find that the history
of, you know, nowadays, you know, uh,
King Charles is very pro-Islamist, you know, pro,
it's not nothing wrong with that. Everything is
fine. And then there were reports about him taking
$3.2 million. I don't know if you've seen that
report. Like he needs the money. Like he needs
the money, but he took $3.2 million. You know,
I hate to say it, Pat. Right there. Look at
this. From between 2011 and 2015, then Prince
Charles received approximately 3.2 $.2 million
in cash payments from Qatari Prime Minister.
This has been confirmed and he said he did, but
he said the moment money went into our account,
we just gave it to charity immediately. There was
no illegal things done. You know, we're supposed
to believe that. So, I wonder the you know, buying
influence if if the government all of a sudden I
don't even know if they would pursue this because
because you know they may not even want that man.
I if somebody was to come out like let's just say
they did this with SPLC. Yeah. Yeah. And all of
a sudden they come out and say, "Let me tell
you guys that these top 50 influencers, who's
funding them, who they're getting money from, it
would silence the entire market and it would the
fog of war in mainstream media and podcast and
today would be gone. Everybody would say, "Okay,
we know why you say what you say. We know where
your position is. Great. Can we all move on? Let's
move forward." This is exactly why we need robust
oversight rather than the cheerleaders on Capitol
Hill that we have. We need people who are really
going to provide independent oversight. Let me
tell you a story and forgive me that I have to
sort of fudge the language a little bit, but I
I need to I had a conversation with a senator a
couple of days ago. Um he uh had somebody reach
out. Can you come up to the office? I said, of
course. I go up there and he's concerned about
some documents. He needed to see some documents.
documents that were classified in the 1970s. I
said, "Well, they they should have been subject
to mandatory declassification. We have a mandatory
declassification law in this country after 30 or
35 years. They have to be declassified unless they
contain the names of a source or um the methods of
an ongoing operation." And he said, "Exactly." And
they've never been declassified. And he said, "I
went to the CIA and they said, "We don't know what
you're talking about. They're not our documents."
And it turns out that they're Senate documents.
Well, the Senate is not the the Congress is not
subject to the Freedom of Information Act and
it's not subject they always exempt themselves
from their own laws, right? So, no laws apply
on Capitol Hill. They do anything they want.
And so, I said, uh, well, why don't you go to
leadership? And he said, I went to leadership
and they said they don't want to get involved
in this fight between two committee chairman.
And I said, ' And the other chairman, he said,
'The other chairman told me to go screw myself.
And I said, 'Are you kidding me? And he said, 'n
no.' He said, 'I don't know what to do. And we sat
there for two hours and we could not come up with
a plan. And it's because there is no oversight.
It's funny to me. You read the Constitution,
the Constitution says that that the government is
made up of three co-equal branches. the executive,
the legislative, and the judicial. But that's just
not how we treat it. The the the the legislative
has seated its authority to the executive. And so
now, if you know there's a Republican in the White
House, Republicans on Capitol Hill are going to do
everything they can to support the the president
and to pass the president's legislation. The
Democrats have somebody in the White House. The
Democrats in Congress are going to do everything
they can to support the president. That's not what
the founding fathers envisioned. Three co-equal
branches and then what we end up with is these
so-called oversight committees that don't oversee
anything. They just egg them on. Yeah, it is. So,
I think I think the the part with America
that when when I hear people that are tired,
I'm like, what are you tired with? What are you
most upset with? I just don't think there's any
accountability. That's exactly the problem. Yeah.
I just don't think there's any accountability.
What do you mean? It seems like they're all on
the same party. Seems like they're all protect.
You hear that message, right? You can't have
that because that's not good in a democracy.
If there's accountability for the average person
that does something and then there isn't for the
other guys. What are you talking about? Yeah. No,
there's not. So, I I I think this administration
uh a story came out. I don't know if you
saw the story came out yesterday saying that
uh again it's a leak that they want
Tulsi to resign after midterms. Okay. So,
they want Tulsi to resign after midterms. All
right. That story was leaked. I don't know if
it's even a story there or not. There you go.
Yeah. Director Donald Trump reportedly wants the
director of national Okay. Who knows what these
stories are? Like we asked you earlier, what
stories do they leak? What do they not? and you
kind of test the market. Who knows what this is,
you know, on on how they're dropping a story. But
to me, if there's anything this administration has
a shot at increasing the score the people have in
the CIA, in the FBI, in the US government a little
bit more because the way it dropped after Kennedy
is a oh my god, it's like a massive from 72% trust
in the FBI. Can you pull up the history of trust
in the US government or trust in the FBI or trust
in the CIA and then Watergate and then Watergate,
you know, one by one by one. Um there's a chart,
Rob, if you go back and just go to images, you'll
see it. Yeah, it's one of those that shows the
high was 72% and I don't know what. Yeah. Zoom in
a little bit if you could. Oh, it doesn't go all
the way back. It doesn't go all the way back. So
that goes from 97. The one I'm looking at is from
the 60s, you know. Uh uh go on the second one.
See what the saying the Pew Research. There you
go. That's the one from 58. Wow. Look at that.
We used to trust 72%. Look at that. We used to
trust the government. We're like, "Yeah, they're
good." You know, they're And then we're now in
the 20s and the teens and that's 15. I would
assume it's even lower today. Like even 911,
it was barely 50%. Yep. Yep. That's right.
Even 911 was 50%. At least we're like, look,
they're the good people. They're here to protect
us. Yeah. That there is a massive mass. And by
the way, I think long-term, the lower that score
goes, you you you you cannot risk not knowing the
consequences of the score getting too low. That's
right. Cuz if it gets too low, then what does
the youth do who don't have anything to lose?
Anything. The youngest is willing to break the
whole thing because they're like, "Well, you know
what? You guys are not doing anything. You guys
are all protecting each other. You guys are wow
and then you're dealing with a bigger problem. So
I hope they do something to regain the faith. Hi
everybody. I'm John Kuryaku, former CIA officer.
Please find me on MC. We have a lot to talk
about. CIA, FBI, DoD, torture, secret prisons,
international renditions. Maybe you or your child
want to apply for a job at the CIA and are looking
for some tips. Let me know. There's a lot we can
talk about. You pick the subject, we'll make it
happen. Again, it's on MCT. Thanks and I'll see
you soon. If you enjoyed this video, you want to
watch more videos like this, click here. And if
you want to watch the entire podcast, click here.